Wyck Association Collection 1663-1972 Mss.Ms.Coll.52
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Correspondence, 1676-1971; 31.0 Linear feet 80 boxes
  - To: Jane Bowne Haines I
    - 1815 Apr.3-1815 Jul.3 (Box 22, Folder 310)
    - 1815 Sep.10-1815 Dec.24 (Box 22, Folder 311)
    - 1816 Feb.13-1816 Oct.5 (Box 22, Folder 312)
    - 1816 Nov.5-1816 Dec.15 (Box 22, Folder 313)
    - 1817 Jan.21-1817 Mar.20 (Box 22, Folder 314)
    - 1817 Apr. 30- 1817 May 29 (Box 22, Folder 315)
    - 1817 Jun. 2- 1817 Jul. 31 (Box 22, Folder 316)
    - 1817 Aug. 5- 1817 Oct. 29 (Box 22, Folder 317)
    - 1817 Nov. 1- 1817 Dec. 30 (Box 22, Folder 318)
    - 1818 Jan. 8- 1818 Feb. 27 (Box 22, Folder 319)
    - 1818 Mar. 8- 1818 May 26 (Box 22, Folder 320)
    - 1818 Jun. 5- 1818 Aug. 29 (Box 22, Folder 321)
    - 1818 Sep. 3- 1818 Dec. 24 (Box 22, Folder 322)
    - 1819 Jan. 3- 1819 Mar. 12 (Box 22, Folder 323)
    - Henry Hudson, 1819 Apr. 2- 1819 May 30 (Box 22, Folder 324)
    - 1819 Jul. 19- 1819 Nov. 12 (Box 22, Folder 325)
    - 1820 Jan. 2- 1820 Mar. 29 (Box 22, Folder 326)
    - 1820 Apr. 2- 1820 Jun. 30 (Box 22, Folder 327)
    - 1820 Jul. 4- 1820 Dec. 31 (Box 22, Folder 328)
    - 1821 Jan. 18 1821 May 26 (Box 22, Folder 329)
    - 1821 Jul. 16- 1821 Dec. 14 (Box 22, Folder 330)
    - 1822 Jan. 13- 1822 May 20 (Box 22, Folder 331)
    - 1822 Jun. 9- 1822 Aug. 31 (Box 22, Folder 332)
    - 1822 Sep. 7- 1822 Nov. 27 (Box 23, Folder 333)
    - Wedding reception menu; James Mott, 1823 Jan. 3- 1823 May 26 (Box 23, Folder 334)
    - Floor coverings, 1823 Jun. 5- 1823 Dec. 27 (Box 23, Folder 335)
    - William Strickland, 1824 Jan. 22- 1824 Jul. 23 (Box 23, Folder 336)
    - 1824 Aug. 1- 1824 Nov. 28 (Box 23, Folder 337)
    - 1824 Dec. 1- 1824 Dec. 28 (Box 23, Folder 338)
    - Charles and Joseph Bonaparte; "Duke of Saxe-Weimar"; Thomas Eddy, 1825 Jan. 4- 1825 Dec. 25 (Box 23, Folder 339)
    - Robert Owen; New Harmony, 1826 Jan. 13- 1826 Jul. 17 (Box 23, Folder 340)
    - 1826 Sep. 5- 1826 Dec. 25 (Box 23, Folder 341)
    - 1827 Jan. 8- 1827 Jun. 30 (Box 23, Folder 342)
    - 1827 Jul. 13- 1827 Dec. 26 (Box 23, Folder 343)
    - 1828 Jan. 15- 1828 Jul. 16 (Box 23, Folder 344)
    - 1828 Aug. 22- 1828 Nov. 24 (Box 23, Folder 345)
    - Mary Ann Donaldson, 1829 Jan. 5- 1829 Aug. 19 (Box 23, Folder 346)
    - 1829 Sep. 9- 1829 Nov. 24 (Box 23, Folder 347)
    - 1830 Feb. 26- 1830 Dec. 25 (Box 23, Folder 348)
    - 1831 Jan. 23- 1831 May 23. (Box 23, Folder 349)
    - 1831 Aug. 30- 1831 Nov. 12 (Box 23, Folder 350)
    - American Institute of Instruction, 1832 Jan. 9- 1832 Apr. 11 (Box 23, Folder 351)
    - Abba Alcott, 1832 Jun. 3- 1832 Dec. 16 (Box 23, Folder 352)
    - Wyck plants; T. Nuttall, 1833 Jan. 3- 1833 Jul. 27 (Box 23, Folder 353)
    - 1833 Aug. 2- 1833 Nov. 21 (Box 23, Folder 354)
    - 1834 Jan. 1- 1834 Dec. 19 (Box 23, Folder 355)
    - 1835 Jan. 4- 1835 Dec. 31 (Box 24, Folder 356)
    - 1836 Jan. 1- 1836 Aug. 28 (Box 24, Folder 357)
    - 1837 Jan. 24 1837 Dec. 10 (Box 24, Folder 358)
    - 1838 Apr. 11- 1838 Dec. 16 (Box 24, Folder 359)
    - 1839 Jan. 3- 1839 Nov. 26 (Box 24, Folder 360)
    - 1840 Mar. 18- 1840 Dec. 26 (Box 24, Folder 361)
    - 1841 Jan. 3- 1841 Dec. 14 (Box 24, Folder 362)
    - 1842 Jan.18-1842 Dec.24 (Box 24, Folder 363)
    - 1843 Jan.16-1843 Dec.7 (Box 24, Folder 364)
    - n.d. (Box 24, Folder 365)
  - From: Ann Haines
    - 1806 Dec.9-1811 Apr.7 (Box 25, Folder 366)
    - Laying brick at Wyck House, 1814 Jul.21-1815 Sep.26 (Box 25, Folder 367)
    - Sale of Dr. Joseph Priestly's library, 1816 Apr.5-1816 Dec.26 (Box 25, Folder 368)
    - Gas lights, 1817 Jan.2-1817 May 4 (Box 25, Folder 369)
    - 1818 Jul.5-1818 Dec.31 (Box 25, Folder 370)
    - Harmony Society, 1820 Jul.2-1822 Sep.16 (Box 25, Folder 371)
    - Pa. School for Deaf; John Fanning Watson, 1823 Oct.26-1823 Nov.14 (Box 25, Folder 372)
    - Alteration and garden at Wyck; illness of R.H.; Lafayette; grates; fenders and doorknobs for Wyck, 1824 Apt.22-1824 Oct.4 (Box 25, Folder 373)
    - Household; William Maclure, 1826 May 24-1827 Oct.21 (Box 25, Folder 374)
    - Hicksite vs. Orthodox Friends, 1829 May 15-1830 Nov.10 (Box 25, Folder 375)
    - 1831 Jun.21-1832 Dec.26 (Box 25, Folder 376)
    - 1833 Jan.5-1833 Nov. (Box 25, Folder 377)
    - 1834 Feb.9-1834 Nov.29 (Box 25, Folder 378)
    - 1836 Aug.17-1837 Oct.24 (Box 25, Folder 379)
    - 1840 Jan.18-1841 Dec.31 (Box 25, Folder 380)
    - 1842 May 15-1842 Oct.19 (Box 25, Folder 381)
    - 1843 Nov.23-1845 Feb.3 (Box 25, Folder 382)
    - 1852 Feb.28-1859 Sep.25 (Box 25, Folder 383)
    - 1860 Oct.2-1867 Jul.1 (Box 25, Folder 384)
  - To: Ann Haines
    - 1804 Mar.17-1809 Jul.31 (Box 26, Folder 385)
    - 1810 Mar.29-1810 Dec.3 (Box 26, Folder 386)
    - 1811 Apr.20-1812 Nov.19 (Box 26, Folder 387)
    - 1813 Jan.8-1813 Dec.23 (Box 26, Folder 388)
    - 1814 Feb.3 1814 Dec.11 (Box 26, Folder 389)
    - 1815 Mar.24-1815 Sep.4 (Box 26, Folder 390)
    - 1816 May 2-1817 Dec.18 (Box 26, Folder 391)
    - 1818 Jan.21-1819 Nov.4 (Box 26, Folder 392)
    - 1820 Feb.10-1820 Oct.26 (Box 26, Folder 393)
    - 1821 Jan.13-1821 May 31 (Box 26, Folder 394)
    - 1821 Jun.11-1821 Dec.11 (Box 26, Folder 395)
    - 1822 Jan.24-1822 Dec.12 (Box 26, Folder 396)
    - 1823 Feb.21 1823 Oct.10 (Box 26, Folder 397)
    - 1824 Jan.29-1824 Nov.30 (Box 26, Folder 398)
    - 1825 Jan.16-1825 Nov.29 (Box 26, Folder 399)
    - 1826 May 4-1826 Nov.14 (Box 26, Folder 400)
    - 1827 Apr.5-1827 Nov.25 (Box 26, Folder 401)
    - 1828 Jan.17-1828 Oct.16 (Box 26, Folder 402)
    - 1929 Jan.19-1829 Jul.14 (Box 27, Folder 403)
    - 1830 Mar.26-1830 Nov.23 (Box 26, Folder 404)
    - 1831 Feb.5-1831 Nov.27 (Box 27, Folder 405)
    - 1832 Jan.16 1832 Sep.17 (Box 27, Folder 406)
    - 1833 Mar.24-1833 Dec. (Box 27, Folder 407)
    - 1834 Jan.2-1834 Dec.25 (Box 27, Folder 408)
    - 1835 Jul.15-1835 Oct.15 (Box 27, Folder 409)
    - 1836 Jan.19-1836 Dec.14 (Box 27, Folder 410)
    - 1837 Jan.31-1837 May 15 (Box 27, Folder 411)
    - 1837 Jun.5-1837 Nov.21 (Box 27, Folder 412)
    - 1838 Jan.23-1838 Nov.16 (Box 27, Folder 413)
    - 1839 Mar. 3-1839 Jul.15 (Box 27, Folder 414)
    - 1839 Jan.14-1839 Oct.9 (Box 27, Folder 415)
    - 1840 Jan.25-1840 Apr.12 (Box 27, Folder 416)
    - 1840 Apr.14-1840 Jul.8 (Box 27, Folder 417)
    - 1841 Feb.1-1841 Oct.13 (Box 27, Folder 418)
    - 1842 Mar.17-1842 Sep.1 (Box 27, Folder 419)
    - 1844 Jan.18-1844 Dec.25 (Box 27, Folder 420)
    - 1845 Jan.13-1845 Aug.22 (Box 27, Folder 421)
    - 1845 Sep.6-1845 Nov.6 (Box 27, Folder 422)
    - 1846 Apr.29-1846 Dec.8 (Box 27, Folder 423)
    - 1847 Mar.9 1849 Feb.29 (Box 27, Folder 424)
    - 1852 Dec.13-1863 Sep.7 (Box 27, Folder 425)
  - From: John Aston Warder
    - 1872 Feb. 2 (Box 28, Folder 426)
  - To: John Aston Warder
    - 1880 Nov.22, 1883 Jan.26, 1883 Feb.6 (Box 28, Folder 427)
  - From: Sarah M. Haines
    - 1819 Oct.16-1823 Dec. (Box 28, Folder 428)
    - Lafayette's visit to Philadelphia, 1824 Apr.18-1824 Sep.7 (Box 28, Folder 429)
    - Peale Museum, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 430)
  - To: Sarah M. Haines
    - 1826 Oct.4-1821 Mar.25 (Box 28, Folder 431)
    - 1822 Oct.15-1823 Nov.23 (Box 28, Folder 432)
    - n.d. (Box 28, Folder 433)
  - From: William Henry Bacon
    - 1845 Apr.13-1849 Dec.11 (Box 29, Folder 434)
  - To: William Henry Bacon
    - 1842 Nov.25-1861 Aug.26 (Box 29, Folder 435)
    - 1864 Feb.2-1872 Aug.16 (Box 29, Folder 436)
  - From: Elizabeth Bowne Haines Warder
    - 1826 Apr.23-1834 May 1 (Box 29, Folder 437)
    - 1835 Feb.17-1842 Apr.6 (Box 29, Folder 438)
    - Civil War, 1844 Feb.5-1866 Aug.23 (Box 29, Folder 439)
    - 1867 Feb.20-1883 Dec.3 (Box 29, Folder 440)
    - 1886 Nov.14-1889 Dec.12 (Box 29, Folder 441)
  - To: Elizabeth Bowne Haines Warder
    - 1845 Apr. 14 (Box 29, Folder 442)
  - From: John Smith Haines II
    - 1830 Sep.29-1833 May 17 (Box 30, Folder 443)
    - 1836 Aug.14-1839 Dec.16 (Box 30, Folder 444)
    - Discusses possibility of tearing down brewhouse, 1841 Dec.11-1842 Dec.5 (Box 30, Folder 445)
    - 1843 Jan.13-1859 Dec.26 (Box 30, Folder 446)
    - 1860 Aug.24-1870 Nov.29 (Box 30, Folder 447)
    - 1871 Mar.6-1886 Dec.27 (Box 30, Folder 448)
    - n.d. (Box 30, Folder 449)
  - To: John Smith Haines II
    - 1832 Oct.19-1839 Jan.23 (Box 30, Folder 450)
    - 1840 Mar.28-1843 Dec.19 (Box 30, Folder 451)
    - 1844 Jan.5-1852 Apr.6 (Box 30, Folder 452)
    - 1854 May 8-1858 Dec.1 (Box 30, Folder 453)
    - 1860 Oct.2-1863 (Box 30, Folder 454)
    - 1864 Sep.10-1871 Sep.1 (Box 30, Folder 455)
    - 1873 Mar.8-1884 Mar.3 (Box 30, Folder 456)
  - From: Hannah Haines Bacon
    - 1830 Oct.6-1842 Nov.8 (Box 31, Folder 457)
    - See: From. Jane Bowne Haines "Dadnerreotype", 1839 Dec 7 (Box 20, Folder 283)
    - Trip to Washington, 1845 Feb.24-c.1890 (Box 31, Folder 458)
  - To: Hannah Haines Bacon
    - 1845 May 11-1877 Dec.26 (Box 31, Folder 459)
  - From: Robert B. Haines I
    - Haverford School; daguerreotype, 1834 Jul.9-1844 Aug.21 (Box 32, Folder 460)
      (See Box 20, Folder 283 Nov.19,1839 for other ref. to dagnerreotype)
    - Travel, 1845 May 20-1849 Jun.11 (Box 32, Folder 461)
    - 1850 Jun.28-1853 Sep.12 (Box 32, Folder 462)
    - 1856 Jun.23-1860 Jun.2 (Box 32, Folder 463)
    - 1862 Sep.21-1864 Aug.1 (Box 32, Folder 464)
    - 1865 Jul.18-1867 Oct.15 (Box 32, Folder 465)
    - Dr. Wistar, Thomas R. Meehan, 1868 Jul.30-1868 Dec.14 (Box 32, Folder 466)
    - State of the South after the Civil War, 1869 Jan.14-1869 Dec.18 (Box 32, Folder 467)
    - Religious meetings in the South with Isaac Robson to the Freedman, 1870 Jan.15-1870 Nov.10 (Box 32, Folder 468)
    - Religious meetings in the South with Isaac Robson to the Freedman, 1870 Dec.2-1870 Dec.26 (Box 32, Folder 469)
    - Society of Friends Quarterly Meeting, 1871 Mar.30-1872 Nov.20 (Box 32, Folder 470)
    - 1883 Feb.7-1873 Dec.20 (Box 32, Folder 471)
    - 1874 Feb.20-1874 Nov.13 (Box 32, Folder 472)
    - 1875 Jan.13-1875 Jun.30 (Box 32, Folder 473)
    - 1875 Jul.2-1875 Nov.26 (Box 32, Folder 474)
    - 1877 May 1-1878 Sep.2 (Box 32, Folder 475)
    - 1880 Sep.18-1883 Jul.23 (Box 32, Folder 476)
    - 1885 Apr.21-1889 Oct.6 (Box 32, Folder 477)
    - 1890 Jun.27-1894 Nov.17 (Box 32, Folder 478)
  - To: Robert B. Haines I
    - William Russell, 1838 Jan.4-1849 Jun.11 (Box 33, Folder 479)
    - 1838 May 11 (Box 33, Folder 480)
    - 1845 Mar.20 (Box 33, Folder 481)
    - 1853 Jan.26-1854 Jan.11 (Box 33, Folder 482)
    - 1856 Nov.26-1859 Oct.15 (Box 33, Folder 483)
    - 1863 Jul.13-1864 Oct.5 (Box 33, Folder 484)
    - 1866 Nov.26-1870 Nov.22 (Box 33, Folder 485)
    - James E. Rhoads, 1871 Apr.21-1872 Oct.4 (Box 33, Folder 486)
    - James E. Rhoads, 1872 Nov.25-1873 Dec.26 (Box 33, Folder 487)
    - 1874 Jan.6-1874 May 27 (Box 33, Folder 488)
    - James E. Rhoads, 1874 Jun.4-1875 Nov.20 (Box 33, Folder 489)
    - 1876 May 1-1876 Dec.21 (Box 33, Folder 490)
    - 1877 May 14-1879 Jul.5 (Box 33, Folder 491)
    - 1880 Jan.27 1881 Sep.30 (Box 33, Folder 492)
    - 1882 Dec.24-1885 Aug.20 (Box 33, Folder 493)
    - 1886 Feb.1-1887 Dec.13 (Box 33, Folder 494)
    - 1888 Jan.15-1889 Feb.18 (Box 33, Folder 495)
    - 1889 Feb.25-1889 Apr.18 (Box 33, Folder 496)
    - 1890 Jan.8-1890 Mar.4 (Box 33, Folder 497)
    - 1891 Jan.8-1891 Dec.14 (Box 33, Folder 498)
    - 1892 Jan.4-1892 Dec.25 (Box 33, Folder 499)
    - 1893 Jan.7-1893 Oct.31 (Box 33, Folder 500)
    - 1894 Dec.26-1895 Nov.15 (Box 33, Folder 501)
    - n.d. (Box 33, Folder 502)
  - From: Margaret Haines Stewardson
    - Ornithology; Henry Clay, 1837 Apr.27-1848 Oct.3 (Box 34, Folder 503)
    - Wyck garden; trip to England, 1849 Feb.29-1869 Feb.23 (Box 34, Folder 504)
  - To: Margaret Haines Stewardson
    - 1834 Nov.2 (Box 34, Folder 505)
  - From: Thomas Stewardson II
    - 1886 Aug.31-1899 Aug.22 (Box 34, Folder 506)
  - To: Thomas Stewardson II
    - 1872 Apt.11-1899 Apr.24 (Box 34, Folder 507)
  - From: Margaret Vaux Wistar Haines
    - 1846 May 27-1849 Apr.22 (Box 35, Folder 508)
    - 1850 Mar.4-1850 Jul.23 (Box 35, Folder 509)
    - 1859 Oct.4 1865 Dec.5 (Box 35, Folder 510)
    - 1866 Jun.17-1866 Nov.16 (Box 35, Folder 511)
    - 1867 Jan.16-1867 Jun.28 (Box 35, Folder 512)
    - Westtown School, 1867 Jul.1-1867 Jul.29 (Box 35, Folder 513)
    - 1867 Aug.3-1867 Dec.15 (Box 35, Folder 514)
    - 1868 Jan.12-1868 May 29 (Box 35, Folder 515)
    - 1868 Jun.5-1868 Sep.11 (Box 35, Folder 516)
    - 1869 Mar.19-1869 May 21 (Box 35, Folder 517)
    - 1869 Jun. 1-1869 Oct.22 (Box 35, Folder 518)
    - 1869 Nov.27-1869 Dec.31 (Box 35, Folder 519)
    - 1870 Jan.27-1870 Nov.11 (Box 35, Folder 520)
    - 1871 May 26 (Box 35, Folder 521)
    - 1872 Jun.13-1872 Oct.18 (Box 35, Folder 522)
    - 1872 Nov.6-1872 Dec.17 (Box 35, Folder 523)
    - 1873 Jan.6-1873 Apr.4 (Box 35, Folder 524)
    - 1873 May 19-1873 Nov.14 (Box 35, Folder 525)
    - 1874 Jan.22-1874 Jun.11 (Box 35, Folder 526)
    - 1874 Jun.14-1874 Aug.20 (Box 35, Folder 527)
    - 1874 Sep.9-1874 Dec.30 (Box 35, Folder 528)
    - 1875 Jan.8-1875 Feb.25 (Box 36, Folder 529)
    - 1875 Mar.2-1875 Jun.30 (Box 36, Folder 530)
    - 1875 Jul.1-1875 Sep.9 (Box 36, Folder 531)
    - 1876 Aug.21 (Box 36, Folder 532)
    - 1877 Jul.22 (Box 36, Folder 533)
    - 1878 Jul.17-1878 Sep.4 (Box 36, Folder 534)
    - 1880 Jul.9-1880 Dec.16 (Box 36, Folder 535)
    - 1881 Jan.5-1881 Mar.24 (Box 36, Folder 536)
    - 1881 Apr.4-1881 Jun.26 (Box 36, Folder 537)
    - Trip to Europe, 1881 Jul.2-1881 Dec.22 (Box 36, Folder 538)
    - 1883 Aug.11 (Box 36, Folder 539)
    - 1884 Mar.24-1884 Oct.8 (Box 36, Folder 540)
    - 1885 Jul.21-1885 Oct.20 (Box 36, Folder 541)
    - 1886 Mar.20-1886 Jul.3 (Box 36, Folder 542)
    - 1887 Mar.8-1887 Nov.21 (Box 36, Folder 543)
    - 1881 Jan.11 (Box 36, Folder 544)
    - 1889 Jul.9-1889 Dec.9 (Box 36, Folder 545)
    - 1890 Feb.20 (Box 36, Folder 546)
    - 1891 Feb.5-1891 Nov.2 (Box 36, Folder 547)
    - the Trolley system, 1892 Jan.12-1892 Jun.4 (Box 36, Folder 548)
    - 1893 Mar.21-1893 Dec.6 (Box 36, Folder 549)
    - 1894 Feb.14-1894 Jul.27 (Box 36, Folder 550)
    - 1895 Sep.23-1895 Nov.18 (Box 36, Folder 551)
    - 1896 Sep.14 (Box 36, Folder 552)
    - 1897 Jul.7-1897 Dec.7 (Box 36, Folder 553)
    - 1898 Jan.15-1898 May 23 (Box 36, Folder 554)
    - 1898 Jun3-1898 Dec.13 (Box 36, Folder 555)
    - 1899 Feb.10-1899 May 17 (Box 36, Folder 556)
    - 1899 Jun.2-1899 Dec.23 (Box 36, Folder 557)
    - 1900 Jan.2-1900 May 31 (Box 37, Folder 558)
    - 1900 Jun.9 1900 Dec.6 (Box 37, Folder 559)
    - 1901 Jan.2-1901 May 27 (Box 37, Folder 560)
    - 1901 Jun.5-1901 Dec.7 (Box 37, Folder 561)
    - 1902 Feb.10 1902 Jun.3 (Box 37, Folder 562)
    - 1902 Jun.6 (Box 37, Folder 563)
    - 1903 Jan.14-1903 Dec.23 (Box 37, Folder 564)
    - 1904 Jan.29-1904 Mar.21 (Box 37, Folder 565)
    - 1904 Apr.12 (Box 37, Folder 566)
    - 1905 Mar.15 (Box 37, Folder 567)
    - 1905 May 27-1905 Sep.24 (Box 37, Folder 568)
    - 1905 Oct.2-1905 Mar.15 (Box 37, Folder 569)
    - 1906 Jan.1-1906 Mar.27 (Box 37, Folder 570)
    - 1906 Apr.11-1906 May 28 (Box 37, Folder 571)
    - 1906 Aug.3-1906 Dec.11 (Box 37, Folder 572)
    - 1907 Jan.26-1907 Jun.10 (Box 37, Folder 573)
    - 1908 Dec.1 1908 Dec.30 (Box 37, Folder 574)
    - 1909 Jan.5-1909 Dec.12 (Box 37, Folder 575)
    - 1910 Jan.6-1910 Dec.20 (Box 37, Folder 576)
    - 1911 Jan.4 (Box 37, Folder 577)
    - 1912 Jan.11 (Box 37, Folder 578)
    - 1913 Jan.2-1913 Dec.23 (Box 37, Folder 579)
    - 1914 Jan.5-1914 Mar.20 (Box 37, Folder 580)
    - 1914 Mar.23-1914 Dec.2 (Box 37, Folder 581)
    - 1915 Jan.4 (Box 37, Folder 582)
    - 1916 Feb.15-1916 Sep.8 (Box 37, Folder 583)
    - 1917 Jul.24-1917 Mar.5 (Box 37, Folder 584)
    - n.d. (Box 37, Folder 585)
    - n.d. (Box 37, Folder 586)
    - n.d. (Box 37, Folder 587)
    - n.d. (Box 37, Folder 588)
  - To: Margaret Vaux Wistar Haines
    - 1840 Feb.5 (Box 38, Folder 589)
    - 1842 Jan.1 (Box 38, Folder 590)
    - 1843 Jan.10 (Box 38, Folder 591)
    - 1844 Apr.14-1844 Aug.21 (Box 38, Folder 592)
    - 1845 Jan.10-1845 Dec.8 (Box 38, Folder 593)
    - 1846 Jan.5-1846 Dec. (Box 38, Folder 594)
    - 1847 Aug.9 (Box 38, Folder 595)
    - c.1848-1852 (Box 38, Folder 596)
    - c.1848-1852 (Box 38, Folder 597)
    - c.1848-1852 (Box 38, Folder 598)
    - c.1848-1852 (Box 38, Folder 599)
    - 1848 Jan.27-1848 Oct.12 (Box 38, Folder 600)
    - 1849 Jan.1 (Box 38, Folder 601)
    - 1850 Mar.26 (Box 38, Folder 602)
    - 1850 Aug.27-1850 Oct.15 (Box 38, Folder 603)
    - 1851 Jan.3-1851 Jun.19 (Box 38, Folder 604)
    - 1851 Jul.3-1851 Dec.25 (Box 38, Folder 605)
    - 1852 Jan.31-1852 Dec.18 (Box 38, Folder 606)
    - 1853 Jan.2-1853 Dec.5 (Box 38, Folder 607)
    - 1854 Jan.11-1854 Dec.27 (Box 38, Folder 608)
    - 1855 Jan.2-1855 Nov.11 (Box 38, Folder 609)
    - 1856 Jan.9-1856 Dec.26 (Box 38, Folder 610)
    - 1857 Jan.20-1857 Nov.9 (Box 38, Folder 611)
    - 1858 May 18-1858 Nov.25 (Box 38, Folder 612)
    - 1859 Feb.14-1859 Apr. (Box 38, Folder 613)
    - 1859 Sep.14-1859 Dec.25 (Box 38, Folder 614)
    - 1860 Feb.10-1860 Mar.19 (Box 38, Folder 615)
    - 1861 Jan.1-1861 Dec-16 (Box 38, Folder 616)
    - 1862 Feb.18-1862 Dec.21 (Box 38, Folder 617)
    - 1863 Jan.4-1863 Nov.1 (Box 38, Folder 618)
    - 1864 Jan.14-1864 Nov.20 (Box 38, Folder 619)
    - 1865 Feb.6-1865 Nov.24 (Box 38, Folder 620)
    - 1866 Jan.29-1866 Dec.13 (Box 38, Folder 621)
    - 1867 Feb.22-1867 Nov.13 (Box 38, Folder 622)
    - 1868 Jan.22-1868 Aug.13 (Box 39, Folder 623)
    - 1869 May 17-1869 Jul.7 (Box 39, Folder 624)
    - 1870 Mar.23-1870 Nov.26 (Box 39, Folder 625)
    - 1870 Dec.5-1870 Dec.28 (Box 39, Folder 626)
    - 1871 Jan.15-1871 Dec.22 (Box 39, Folder 627)
    - 1872 Jan.30-1872 Dec.3 (Box 39, Folder 628)
    - 1873 Jan.25-1873 Sep.9 (Box 39, Folder 629)
    - 1874 Jan.14-1874 Dec.2 (Box 39, Folder 630)
    - 1875 Jan.2-1875 Jul.18 (Box 39, Folder 631)
    - 1875 Sep.7-1875 Dec.30 (Box 39, Folder 632)
    - 1876 Jan.9-1876 Aug.30 (Box 39, Folder 633)
    - 1876 Sep.7-1876 Dec.6 (Box 39, Folder 634)
    - 1877 Jan.14-1877 May 30 (Box 39, Folder 635)
    - 1877 Jun.6-1877 Sep.15 (Box 39, Folder 636)
    - 1877 Sep.16-1877 Dec.12 (Box 39, Folder 637)
    - 1878 Jan.7-1878 Feb.27 (Box 39, Folder 638)
    - 1878 Mar.1-1788 Jul.8 (Box 39, Folder 639)
    - 1878 Aug.4-1878 Dec.31 (Box 39, Folder 640)
    - 1879 Jan.8-1879 Jul.18 (Box 39, Folder 641)
    - 1880 Jan.1-1880 Jul.21 (Box 39, Folder 642)
    - 1880 Aug.10-1880 Dec.27 (Box 40, Folder 643)
    - 1881 Jan.19-1881 May 18 (Box 40, Folder 644)
    - 1881 Aug.19-1881 Nov.1 (Box 40, Folder 645)
    - 1882 Jan.7-1882 Dec.24 (Box 40, Folder 646)
    - 1883 Jan.8-1883 Dec.21 (Box 40, Folder 647)
    - 1884 Jan.3-1884 Jul.23 (Box 40, Folder 648)
    - 1884 Aug.15-1884 Dec.25 (Box 40, Folder 649)
    - 1885 Jan.20-1885 Jul.16 (Box 40, Folder 650)
    - 1885 Aug.16-1885 Dec.8 (Box 40, Folder 651)
    - 1886 Jan.4-1886 May 11 (Box 40, Folder 652)
    - 1886 Jun.12-1886 Dec.30 (Box 40, Folder 653)
    - 1887 Jan.1-1887 Feb.21 (Box 40, Folder 654)
    - 1887 Mar.9-1887 Jun.27 (Box 40, Folder 655)
    - 1887 Jul.3-1887 Aug.24 (Box 40, Folder 656)
    - 1887 Sep.23-1887 Dec.30 (Box 40, Folder 657)
    - 1888 Jan.16-1888 Mar.31 (Box 40, Folder 658)
    - 1888 Apr.2-1888 Jul.28 (Box 40, Folder 659)
    - 1888 Aug.4-1888 Oct.8 (Box 40, Folder 660)
    - 1888 Oct.9-1888 Dec.1 (Box 40, Folder 661)
    - 1889 Jan.10-1889 May.29 (Box 40, Folder 662)
    - 1889 Apr.1-1889 May 19 (Box 40, Folder 663)
    - 1889 Jun.6-1889 Sep.27 (Box 40, Folder 664)
    - 1889 Oct.3-1889 Dec.31 (Box 40, Folder 665)
    - 1890 Jan.8-1890 Feb.14 (Box 40, Folder 666)
    - 1890 Mar.16-1890 Nov.21 (Box 41, Folder 667)
    - 1891 Jan.7-1891 Jul.31 (Box 41, Folder 668)
    - 1891 Aug.4-1891 Dec.28 (Box 41, Folder 669)
    - 1892 Jan.24-1892 Oct.25 (Box 41, Folder 670)
    - 1893 Jan.5-1893 Jun.13 (Box 41, Folder 671)
    - 1893 Jul.8-1893 Aug.24 (Box 41, Folder 672)
    - 1893 Sep.28-1893 Dec.26 (Box 41, Folder 673)
    - 1894 Jan.17-1894 Dec.29 (Box 41, Folder 674)
    - 1895 Jan.13-1895 Sep.30 (Box 41, Folder 675)
    - 1895 Oct.5-1895 Dec.14 (Box 41, Folder 676)
    - 1896 Jan.4-1896 Apr.21 (Box 41, Folder 677)
    - 1896 Apt.5-1896 Jun.25 (Box 41, Folder 678)
    - 1896 Jul.6 1896 Aug.16 (Box 41, Folder 679)
    - 1896 Sep.10-1896 Oct.27 (Box 41, Folder 680)
    - 1896 Nov.1-1896 Dec.27 (Box 41, Folder 681)
    - 1897 Jan.5-1897 Apr.29 (Box 41, Folder 682)
    - 1897 May 3-1897 Jun.29 (Box 41, Folder 683)
    - 1897 Jul.6-1897 Aug.27 (Box 41, Folder 684)
    - 1897 Sep.19-1897 Dec.30 (Box 41, Folder 685)
    - 1898 Jan.2-1898 Apr.27 (Box 42, Folder 686)
    - 1898 Jul.31-1898 Sep.25 (Box 42, Folder 687)
    - 1898 Oct.9-1898 Dec.29 (Box 42, Folder 688)
    - 1899 Jan.13 1899 May 9 (Box 42, Folder 689)
    - 1899 Jun.60 1899 Sep.29 (Box 42, Folder 690)
    - 1899 Sep.1-1899 Dec.29 (Box 42, Folder 691)
    - 1900 Jan.10-1900 Aug.21 (Box 41, Folder 692)
    - 1900 Oct.2-1900 Dec.21 (Box 42, Folder 693)
    - 1901 Mar.10-1901 Dec. 30 (Box 42, Folder 694)
    - 1902 Jan.15-1902 Dec.26 (Box 42, Folder 695)
    - 1903 Jan.16-1903 Dec.30 (Box 42, Folder 696)
    - 1903 Feb.5-1903 Mar.20 (Box 42, Folder 697)
    - 1903 Apr.22-1903 Dec.27 (Box 42, Folder 698)
    - 1904 Jan.7-1904 Jun.26 (Box 42, Folder 699)
    - 1905 Jan.31-1905 Dec.26 (Box 42, Folder 700)
    - 1906 Jan.31-1906 Jul.30 (Box 42, Folder 701)
    - 1906 Aug.7-1906 Oct.7 (Box 42, Folder 702)
    - 1907 Feb.18-1907 Dec.21 (Box 42, Folder 703)
    - 1908 Feb.15-1908 Feb.18 (Box 42, Folder 704)
    - 1909 Jan.26-1909 Jun.9 (Box 43, Folder 705)
    - 1910 Feb.26-1910 Dec.22 (Box 43, Folder 706)
    - 1911 Jan.9-1911 Nov.30 (Box 43, Folder 707)
    - 1912 Feb.21 1912 Dec.28 (Box 43, Folder 708)
    - 1913 Jan.26-1913 Dec.24 (Box 43, Folder 709)
    - 1914 Jan.9-1914 Nov.25 (Box 43, Folder 710)
    - 1915 Jan.19-1915 Dec.28 (Box 43, Folder 711)
    - 1916 Jan.6-1916 Dec.8 (Box 43, Folder 712)
    - 1917 Jan.18-1917 Dec.10 (Box 43, Folder 713)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 714)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 715)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 716)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 717)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 718)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 719)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 720)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 721)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 722)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 723)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 724)
    - n.d. (Box 43, Folder 725)
  - From: Jane Reuben Haines
    - 1844 Aug.21 (Box 44, Folder 726)
    - 1848 Jul.8 (Box 44, Folder 727)
    - 1851 Aug.28-1853 Jan.13 (Box 44, Folder 728)
    - 1856-1859 Dec.31 (Box 44, Folder 729)
    - 1860 Jan.16-1860 May 24 (Box 44, Folder 730)
    - 1861 Dec.3-1863 Sep.4 (Box 44, Folder 731)
    - 1864 Jun.19-1865 May 2 (Box 44, Folder 732)
    - 1866 Feb.1-1868 (Box 44, Folder 733)
    - 1869 Jan.25-1869 Dec.24 (Box 44, Folder 734)
    - 1870 Jan.28-1870 Oct.13 (Box 44, Folder 735)
    - 1871 Jul.21-1875 (Box 44, Folder 736)
    - 1876 Feb.6-1880 (Box 44, Folder 737)
    - 1884 Dec.23-c.1885 (Box 44, Folder 738)
    - 1886 Jul.1-1890 (Box 44, Folder 739)
    - 1891 - 1895 Nov.18 (Box 44, Folder 740)
    - 1896 Jan.9-1900 Dec.27 (Box 44, Folder 741)
    - 1902 Jan.16-1905 Oct.25 (Box 44, Folder 742)
    - 1906 Mar.7-1911 Aug.10 (Box 44, Folder 743)
    - incl. re. Sale of Wyck property, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 744)
  - To: Jane Reuben Haines
    - Charles de Miollis, 1838 Jul.4-1845 Apr.5 (Box 45, Folder 745)
    - 1860 Nov.12-1865 Aug.2 (Box 45, Folder 746)
    - 1868 Aug.-1871 (Box 45, Folder 747)
    - 1872 Jan.23-1873 Aug.21 (Box 45, Folder 748)
    - 1873 Oct.24-1875 (Box 45, Folder 749)
    - 1876 Apt.29-1880 Jun.10 (Box 45, Folder 750)
    - 1881 Jul.22-1883 Nov.28 (Box 45, Folder 751)
    - 1886 Nov.12-1889 Dec.22 (Box 45, Folder 752)
    - 1890 Feb.4-1890 Dec.27 (Box 45, Folder 753)
    - 1891 Jan.23-1891 Dec.25 (Box 45, Folder 754)